Finding Aid for the Sierra Club Angeles Chapter Records LSC.1199
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Sierra Club - Angeles Chapter
  - Desert Protective Council. (Box 139)
  - Colorado River. (Box 139)
  - Colby Library. (Box 139)
  - Club de Exploraciones. (Box 139)
  - Chapter Sections & Groups. (Box 139)
  - Chapter Formation & Earliest Years. (Box 139)
  - Adams, Ansel. (Box 139)
    2 plays.
  - California Desert. (Box 139)
  - Awards--Angeles Chapter. (Box 139)
  - Air Quality. (Box 139)
  - Alaska. (Box 139)
  - Alert (newsletter). (Box 139)
  - Angeles Chapter History Committee. (Box 139)
  - Channel Islands. (Box 139)
  - Annual Reports--Angeles Chapter. (Box 139)
  - Backpacking Committee. (Box 139)
  - Annual Banquet. (Box 139)
  - Banquets. (Box 139)
  - Basecamp. (Box 139)
  - Biographical--Miscellaneous. (Box 139)
  - Bylaws--Angeles Chapter, Groups, Sections. (Box 139)
  - Angeles Chapter Miscellaneous. (Box 139)
    (2 folders)
  - Forest Policies, California. (Box 140)
  - Elections, National. (Box 140)
  - Endangered Species. (Box 140)
  - Little Santa Anita Canyon. (Box 140)
  - Nippomo Dunes. (Box 140)
  - Newport Bay. (Box 140)
  - NCRCC (Northern California Regional Conservation Committee). (Box 140)
  - Natural Science Section. (Box 140)
  - MTC (Mountaineering Training Committee). (Box 140)
  - Mountaineering Committee (National). (Box 140)
  - Mojave Road. (Box 140)
  - Mojave National Park. (Box 140)
  - Mineral King. (Box 140)
  - Membership Surveys. (Box 140)
  - Membership--National & Chapter. (Box 140)
  - Membership Committee & Henniger. (Box 140)
  - Energy. (Box 140)
  - Local Issues--Miscellaneous (Southern California). (Box 140)
  - FCCP Reports. (Box 140)
  - Leadership Training Course. (Box 140)
  - Lassen (Volcanic National Park). (Box 140)
  - Kings Canyon. (Box 140)
  - Kern Plateau. (Box 140)
  - IRS Revocation. (Box 140)
  - History Committee, National. (Box 140)
  - Hazard Park. (Box 140)
  - Grassroots Sierra (publication). (Box 140)
  - Glen Canyon. (Box 140)
  - FWOC (Federation of Western Outdoors Clubs). (Box 140)
  - Fundraising, Angeles Chapter. (Box 140)
  - Friends of Angeles Chapter. (Box 140)
  - Grand Canyon. (Box 140)
  - Los Angeles General Plan. (Box 140)
  - Harwood Lodge. (Box 140)
  - RCCs (NCRCC, SCRCC). (Box 141)
  - Publications Committee, National. (Box 141)
  - Project Flash. (Box 141)
  - Population. (Box 141)
  - Point Reyes. (Box 141)
  - Personnel. (Box 141)
  - Non Sierra Club Organisations. (Box 141)
  - Outings Committee, National. (Box 141)
  - Redwoods National Park. (Box 141)
  - Outdoor Newsletter. (Box 141)
  - Other Chapters. (Box 141)
  - ORVs (Off Road Vehicles). (Box 141)
  - Oregon Dunes. (Box 141)
  - Nuclear Energy. (Box 141)
  - North Cascades. (Box 141)
  - Peripheral Canal. (Box 141)
  - Santa Monica Mountains. (Box 141)
  - Sierra Club Foundation. (Box 141)
  - Sierra Club Books. (Box 141)
  - Sheep Mountain. (Box 141)
  - SCRCC Fundraising, 1978-79. (Box 141)
  - SCCOPE (Political Education). (Box 141)
  - Sierra Club National (Miscellaneous). (Box 141)
  - Recycling. (Box 141)
  - Santa Monica Mountains Task Force & Conservancy. (Box 141)
  - Redwood Mountain. (Box 141)
  - San Rafael Wilderness. (Box 141)
  - San Gorgonio (Wilderness). (Box 141)
  - San Gabriel Wilderness. (Box 141)
  - San Fernando Valley Group. (Box 141)
  - Safety Committee. (Box 141)
  - Robinson Valley. (Box 141)
  - Other Organizations. (Box 141)
  - SCAG Maps. (Box 141)
  - Outings. (Box 141)
  - Tujunga Wash. (Box 142)
  - West Los Angeles Resource District. (Box 142)
  - Watt Campaign. (Box 142)
  - Water Conservation. (Box 142)
  - Water Quality. (Box 142)
  - Waste Management. (Box 142)
  - Volunteers. (Box 142)
  - Viet Nam. (Box 142)
  - White, Georgia. (Box 142)
  - Tule Elk Preserve. (Box 142)
  - Southern California Representative. (Box 142)
  - Training Workshops. (Box 142)
  - Toxic Substances. (Box 142)
  - Tahee. (Box 142)
  - State Parks (California). (Box 142)
  - Ski Mountaineers. (Box 142)
  - Sierra Club Legal Defense Fund. (Box 142)
  - Verdugo Hills Regional Group. (Box 142)
  - Wildlife. (Box 142)
  - Yellowstone. (Box 142)
  - Yes on Nuclear Safeguards Committee. (Box 142)
  - Youth Section. (Box 142)
  - Yosemite. (Box 142)
  - Zion National Park. (Box 142)
  - Brushland Management Lawsuit. (Box 142)
  - Sierra Singles. (Box 142)
  - Wilderness Studies. (Box 142)
- Sierra Club Priorities, A - Z
  - Acid rain. (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural soil preservation. (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Alaska hunting bill. (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Aqua train. (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Big Sur bill. (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - BLM. (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Bradley. (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Bullet train. (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Budget and approps. (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - California Coastal Commission. (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - California convention. (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - California wilderness. (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - Campaigns. (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Clean air. (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Clean costal waters. (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - Clean water act. (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - Coastal zone management. (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence. (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Colorado River. (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Cranston. (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Cranston bill approp. (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Democratic party. (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - DOI (Clark). (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - DOI (Hadel). (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - Environmental organizations. (Box 30, Folder 9)
  - EPA. (Box 30, Folder 10)
  - Energy leasing and conservation. (Box 30, Folder 11)
  - Field offices. (Box 30, Folder 12)
  - Farm bill. (Box 30, Folder 13)
  - Forest planning. (Box 30, Folder 14)
  - Fundraising. (Box 31, Folder 1)
  - Greene, Lorne. (Box 31, Folder 2)
  - Handicapped camping. (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Hazardous Waste. (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Hattoy, Bob. (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Kennard (Centennial). (Box 31, Folder 6)
  - Kem ? Kaweah. (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Mono Lake. (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Mono Lake committe. (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Mono Lake contracts and volunteers. (Box 31, Folder 10)
  - Mono Lake general misc. (Box 31, Folder 11)
  - Mono Lake general publicity. (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - Mono Basin / Lake. (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Mono Lake (DWP). (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Mono Lake lawsuits. (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Mono Lake (agency actions). (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Mono Lake (testimonies and press releases). (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Mono Lake - 97th congress. (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - Mountain lions. (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - Natural forests and BLM planning. (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - National parks. (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - National wilderness. (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - Nevada wilderness. (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - Nuclear waste act. (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - OCS (Current). (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - OCS Lease sale. (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - OCS (General). (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - OCS (Moratorium). (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - OCS (State of California). (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - National parks. (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - National Recreation area. (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Native American TF. (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - News service. (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Newsletter editors copy. (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - ORV's. (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Population issues. (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Mojave group. (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Public lands committee (national). (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - PR. (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Reg VP's forum. (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Sta Margarita river. (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - SCRCC Minutes (v.d., 1981, 1983, 1984). (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - SCRCC Minutes (1970-1979). (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - SCRCC Fundraising. (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Pesticides. (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Press list. (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - PCL. (Box 37, Folder 5)
  - Public land defense. (Box 37, Folder 6)
  - Rare II. (Box 37, Folder 7)
  - Rare III. (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - RCRA. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - SACTO Staff. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - SACTO leg agency. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - San Joaquin. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - San Onofre. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - SB oil pipelines. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Sta Lucia Chapter. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Sta Marguerite. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - SM Mountains. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - SCAG. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Southern California Convention. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Sierra Club (International). (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Sierra Club Foundation. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - SCLDF. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - SCCOPE. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Sierra Club media update. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Environmental Affairs (Gordon Duffy). (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Select Committee on Long-range Policy Planning. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Sewage disposal. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Sierra magazine. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - SINKYONE. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Superfund legislation. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Solid waste. (Box 39, Folder 14)
  - Southwest Sierra Club office. (Box 39, Folder 15)
  - Toxic initiative. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Toxic waste. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Transportation. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Tuolomne river. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Clean water. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Water resources bill. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - White Point. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Wind energy. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Wild rivers. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Wilderness designation. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Wildlife. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Wilderness, ruin of. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - ZEV land use initiative. (Box 40, Folder 13)
- State Parks
  - 18/35-18/42. California State parks (general). (Box 83, Folder 1)
  - Prop 1., (1980) (Box 83, Folder 2)
  - Anza Borrego. (Box 83, Folder 3)
  - Buena Vista Lagoon State Park. (Box 83, Folder 4)
  - Calaveras Big Trees. (Box 83, Folder 5)
  - Chino Hills State Park. (Box 83, Folder 6)
  - Cuyamaca State Park. (Box 83, Folder 7)
  - Emerald Bay State Park. (Box 83, Folder 8)
  - Emma K Wood Beach state park. (Box 83, Folder 9)
  - Franklin Pt (Ano Nuevo State Park). (Box 83, Folder 10)
  - Henry Cove State Park. (Box 83, Folder 11)
  - Nipomo Dunes State Park. (Box 83, Folder 12)
  - 18/42-53. Nipomo (continued). (Box 84, Folder 1)
  - Mt Tamalpais. (Box 84, Folder 2)
  - Pismo Beach. (Box 84, Folder 3)
  - Pt Magu. (Box 84, Folder 4)
  - Rancho Guejiito. (Box 84, Folder 5)
  - Red Rock Canyon. (Box 84, Folder 6)
  - Sta Susanas. (Box 84, Folder 7)
  - Torry Pines. (Box 84, Folder 8)
- Various
  - Newspaper articles. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - California water policy. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Coastal waters. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Water resources conservation and efficiency act. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Porter-Cologne act. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Water planning assumptions. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - California water rights. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Hattoy: general correspondence, letters to elected officials. (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous correspondence. (Box 113, Folder 2)
  - Environmental Movement. (Box 113, Folder 3)
  - Federal lobbying. (Box 113, Folder 4)
  - Los Angeles City Lobbying. (Box 113, Folder 5)
  - Mailers and flyers. (Box 113, Folder 6)
  - Political addresses. (Box 113, Folder 7)
  - Budget. (Box 113, Folder 8)
  - California Lobbying. (Box 113, Folder 9)
  - S/C promotional. (Box 113, Folder 10)
  - Phone bank and outreach. (Box 113, Folder 11)
  - Photo services. (Box 113, Folder 12)
  - Political invitations. (Box 113, Folder 13)
  - Praise and press cong. (Box 113, Folder 14)
  - Press correspondence. (Box 113, Folder 15)
  - Printing. (Box 113, Folder 16)
  - Outside pubs. (Box 113, Folder 17)
  - Research sources. (Box 113, Folder 18)
  - Quarterly reports. (Box 113, Folder 19)
  - International earthcare center. (Box 114, Folder 1)
  - Southern California International Report. (Box 114, Folder 2)
  - Leg. agenda. (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Information services literature lists. (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Sierra club inside. (Box 114, Folder 5)
  - Films. (Box 114, Folder 6)
  - Southern California budgets. (Box 114, Folder 7)
  - McCloskey. (Box 114, Folder 8)
  - Financial statements. (Box 114, Folder 9)
  - California Legislative committees. (Box 114, Folder 10)
  - Reg RCC. (Box 114, Folder 11)
  - Regional RVP's. (Box 114, Folder 12)
  - RCC annual reports and operating procedures. (Box 114, Folder 13)
  - Sierra Club Foundation. (Box 120, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Orgs. (Box 120, Folder 2)
  - A/Q Digest. (Box 120, Folder 3)
  - American Petroleum Institute. (Box 120, Folder 4)
  - AMICOS J Aquarius. (Box 120, Folder 5)
  - Aqueduct. (Box 120, Folder 6)
  - Audubon. (Box 120, Folder 7)
  - BLM Newsbeat. (Box 120, Folder 8)
  - CBE. (Box 120, Folder 9)
  - California Energy Conservation News. (Box 121, Folder 1)
  - California State Coastal Conservancy. (Box 121, Folder 2)
  - California Tomorrow. (Box 121, Folder 3)
  - California Waste Resources. (Box 121, Folder 4)
  - California Department of Water Resources. (Box 121, Folder 5)
  - California Wilderness Commission. (Box 121, Folder 6)
  - Citizens Update on Coastline Policy. (Box 121, Folder 7)
  - Coastline Policy. (Box 121, Folder 8)
  - Committee to Preserve Tule Elk. (Box 121, Folder 9)
  - Concerned Citizens of Owens Valley. (Box 121, Folder 10)
  - Consvervation Federation. (Box 121, Folder 11)
  - Conservation Update. (Box 121, Folder 12)
  - Defenders of Wildlife. (Box 121, Folder 13)
  - Desert Fishes. (Box 121, Folder 14)
  - Desert Survivors. (Box 121, Folder 15)
  - E Mojave Monitors. (Box 121, Folder 16)
  - Desert Tortoise. (Box 121, Folder 17)
  - Council. (Box 122, Folder 1)
  - Ecological Center of Southern California. (Box 122, Folder 2)
  - Edmund G. Brown. (Box 122, Folder 3)
  - Energy grant. (Box 122, Folder 4)
  - Energy depot (California desert district). (Box 122, Folder 5)
  - Energy scene. (Box 122, Folder 6)
  - EDF. (Box 122, Folder 7)
  - Environmental Policy center. (Box 122, Folder 8)
  - NPCA. (Box 122, Folder 9)
  - Federation of Western Outdoor Clubs. (Box 122, Folder 10)
  - Focus on Water. (Box 122, Folder 11)
  - Forest Planning. (Box 122, Folder 12)
  - Forum (SCAG). (Box 122, Folder 13)
  - Friends of the Earth. (Box 122, Folder 14)
  - ?Going public? (Atlantic Richfield). (Box 122, Folder 15)
  - High Country News. (Box 122, Folder 16)
  - Inform. (Box 122, Folder 17)
  - League for Coastal Protection. (Box 122, Folder 18)
  - LCV. (Box 122, Folder 19)
  - Mono Lake News. (Box 122, Folder 20)
  - National Clean air coalition. (Box 122, Folder 21)
  - National Wildlife Federation. (Box 122, Folder 22)
  - NRDC, North Coast Enviromental Center. (Box 122, Folder 23)
  - OSHA Environmental Watch. (Box 122, Folder 24)
  - Outdoors West. (Box 122, Folder 25)
  - Public interest ?Briefs.? (Box 122, Folder 26)
  - Resources for the Future. (Box 122, Folder 27)
  - Salinity update. (Box 122, Folder 28)
  - SANDAG. (Box 122, Folder 29)
  - Save Our Shores. (Box 122, Folder 30)
  - SCAG. (Box 124, Folder 1)
  - Southern Sierra reports. (Box 124, Folder 2)
  - Trust for Public Lands. (Box 124, Folder 3)
  - Union of Concerned Scientists. (Box 124, Folder 4)
  - Wash Monthly. (Box 124, Folder 5)
  - Wash Spectator. (Box 124, Folder 6)
  - Washington Conservation News. (Box 124, Folder 7)
  - Western Waters. (Box 124, Folder 8)
  - Wilderness Society. (Box 124, Folder 9)
  - Alaska. (Box 124, Folder 10)
  - Alaska. (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - Alaska. (Box 126, Folder 1)
  - Genetic engineering. (Box 126, Folder 5)
  - Land use planning. (Box 127, Folder 1-8)
    (8 folders, including BLM and various county folders)
  - Land use planning (continued). (Box 128, Folder 1)
  - Land use planning. (Box 129, Folder 1)
  - Agriculture. (Box 130, Folder 1)
  - Coastal properties 16/26-29b. (Box 130, Folder 2)
  - Coastal (16/30). (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Desert. (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - ORV's. (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - McLane Valley. (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - BLM Desert Recreation Management. (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Barstow to Las Vegas race. (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Ludlow to Parker and Barstow. (Box 132, Folder 1)
  - ORV races. (Box 132, Folder 2)
  - Desert Tales and Guidebooks. (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Desert symposium transcripts. (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - Johnson Valley-Parker. (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Parker 400. (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Desert petroglyphs and artifacts. (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - MX missile. (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Armagosa Valley. (Box 133, Folder 4)
  - E Mojave Planning units. (Box 133, Folder 5)
  - Havasu Natural Wildlife refuge. (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Eureka Dunes and Saline Wilderness. (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Desert Natural Wildlife Range. (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Tahquitz Palm Canyon. (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - YUHA Desert planning. (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Desert Area Military operations. (Box 134, Folder 1)
  - Environmental Law and Litigation (Box 135, Box 136, Box 137)
- Water
  - 25/33-25/41. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - 25/41-25/43. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - 25/43-25/43. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - 25/43-25/49. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - 25/48-25/53. (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - 25/56-25/60. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - 25/61-25/66. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - 25/68-25/69a. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - 25/70-25/80. (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - 25/80-25/85. (Box 73, Folder 1)